Southern Organizing Drives Files 5910
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Southern Organizing Drives Files
1977-1981
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Agre, Louis
Thompson, Ogeltree and Deakin
5910
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5734508
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 15, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5541: Philip Taft Papers 5619/001: ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/007: ACTWU Organizing Department Files 5619/015: ACTWU Department of Occupational Safety and Health Files 5747 mf: Operation Dixie: The CIO Organizing Committee Papers on Microfilm 5760 mf: American Federation of Labor Records, Part 2 on Microfilm 5831 mf: The CIO Files of John L. Lewis, Pt. II: CIO General Files on Microfilm 5918 mf: Minutes of the Executive Council of AFL, Pt. 2 on Microfilm
Agre, Louis; Thompson, Ogeltree; Thompson, Deakin
5734508
- Ogeltree - Thompson, Ogeltree & Deakins (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Captive Audience Speeches (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Ogeltree vs. ACTWU - Badische (cont.), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Ogeltree vs. UBCJA - Veach May Wilson, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  Alcoa, TN
- Ogeltree vs. UBCJA - Visador Co., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Marion, VA
- Ogeltree vs. UCL&GWIU - YKK Inc. (USA), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Macon, GA
- Ogeltree vs. ACTWU - Badische, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Anderson, SC
- Ogeltree vs. USWA - Young Bro. Trucking CO., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Georgetown, SC
- Ogeltree vs. USWA - Dresser Indus. Inc., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Jeffrey Man. Div., Woodruff, SC
- Hanes, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Galax, VA
- Ogeltree vs. ACTWU - Beavertown Knitting, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Selinsgrove, PA
- Ogeltree vs. IBEW - SC Elec. Corp., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Div. Circle F Indus. Pageland, SC
- Ogeltree vs. UPIU - Sampit Lumber Co., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Div. Int'l Paper, SC
- Ogeltree vs. UBCJA - Beirne & Gurdon Lumber Mills, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Div. Int'l Paper, Beirne & Gurdon, AR
- WFSB Editorials, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Bridgeport, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)